“Emergency Medical Center”
Jiwoo, Jiwoo...
Hey, are you awake?
Why am I here?
Why are you…
Why did you do that?
Sister, how are you here?
Why are we…
Kyungdo carried you.
Jiwooya
Dongwon has a fever
I think I should go see it.
Because there is hardness
Get all the treatment and go, okay?
I'm sorry, sister, please go now.
What is sorry...
I feel like my head is going to explode
get me off here
Can you walk?
uh
Hey, Seo Ji-woo
No, why drink and take drugs?
what were you thinking
If it weren't for Seyoung's sister
It almost went to goal
Have the decibels only increased as I got older?
So, that medicine, why did you take it?
Because my mom came
Because I don’t like my mom
I got a little feverish so
my mom is not a good mom
Because I didn’t take the medicine to die.
Don't overdo it
Oh… Over?
Yeah, I overdid it.
I picked him up and ran on his back.
I couldn't sleep
Even if I take sleeping pills, I can’t sleep.
So I ate again
But I can't sleep again
So that's how it happened
Is it true? You said you did that when you were really drunk?
How many times should I say this, Lee Kyung-do, you bastard?
I'm dying of energy
Stir-fry without stopping
Lee Kyung-do, a bastard, an idle bastard
What am I doing, Mr.
go
This crazy guy
Hey
Drinking alcohol and taking an overdose of sleeping pills?
Are you advertising?
Can I write an article for you?
you are being quiet
When a human drinks alcohol
Because it's not enough
It's good in moderation
But go in moderation
There are people who can't do it.
Seo Ji-woo and Lee Kyung are also like these kids.
At a cannabis party in 2018
Why would you go there?
You can't even smoke, huh?
You're so drunk that you get carried away somewhere
They don’t even know they’re going.
I guess you were a smoker
you went so far
I won’t drink unless I have this damn alcohol.
How many sleeping pills do you swallow?
If I get to the point where I can't feel it
That's crazy!
What are you doing, scraping my article?
Going to a fashion show
What about the gum sticking out?
Why are you telling me this all the time?
Hey, try buying this drink again.
Because I will come again and throw it all away
What are you, what do you become?
Whatever happens, it’s love for humanity!
Go, whether I drink
Take drugs or just live without attention.
So, don't drink alcohol!
That
I know it's very difficult
I know best
But you can't drink any more
Very, huh?
It's very difficult
What I'm working on now
A hundred times a thousand times better, do you understand?
I understand
Go, please
Sleep well and order porridge
You did a stomach lavage
You can't eat anything.
Oh, I'm bored.
I understand, so go
The remaining alcohol is gone
You must order porridge
Die! uh?
Look
You said I would look good on you
There's nothing I don't like
By the way
I think this is
It suits me especially well
It's hardness
I cried while wearing this.
Uh…
Because you feel my love?
I felt like you hit me
How much does it cost to carry dishes?
It must have been a hit and run, huh?
hmm…
Not ‘hit and run’ but ‘suffer’
Gee, I like words.
Okay, let's go, I have somewhere to go.
where?
Hey, look at this
yes i color
I thought it would fit perfectly
So pretty
No, if you do this
My gift is fading
Is it ‘give and take’?
Okay, okay.
Give and take, so good, yeah
It's 322,000 won.
How can I help you with payment?
- It's a lump sum payment.
- Oh, yes.
Looks like our couple
This is the color of the dress
That's right, right?
Uh, uh
Receive your card and receipt.
I went there
What about dinner?
Uh, I ate it.
Well done
Hey
I only got 300,000 won this month.
Oh no
Wash my feet, my rotten self
uh
Please call Lee Kyung too, really.
What are you doing, standing there, doing something else?
Hey, it's longitude
You know that trees are the most important thing there, right?
yes
Hold it straight! I'm scared, Mr.
Ah, indeed
- You woke me up.
- Are you doing that all day?
Okay, okay.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
You need to break up, right?
Is the hardness a bit harsh?
This stop is
Dobong-gu Office, Dobong-gu Office
Huh?
I'm coming to your neighborhood
You're tired.
You said you made a stage today
Did you make it well?
uh
I should go see it too
Have you waited long?
Boy, was it worth the wait
uh
We all made it together, right?
Uh, well, what am I?
Just do what you're told, okay?
Did anything interesting happen?
ah… you?
Just been busy, whatever.
Let's eat and go
I didn't eat dinner
Uh…
There's a delicious pork cutlet over there.
Uh, I want to eat tteokbokki.
Let's eat pork cutlet
Since it’s my neighborhood, I’ll buy it for you.
I really like tteokbokki
Let's go in
Why is it not delicious?
no
Why can't I eat if I'm hungry?
Should I just leave? Tonkatsu…
What's wrong with you?
what?
I usually like tteokbokki
You know I like it.
So in our day
Have you ever eaten two meals?
But?
Why am I suddenly not eating well?
Are you asking me to eat pork cutlet?
just
It's good to try something else
I
Because she is the daughter of Jarim Apparel
Are you suddenly uncomfortable eating snacks?
Is it longitude?
I told you I was going to Apgujeong.
Our neighborhood...
This place is closer to school
Why is it in a busy area?
- No, I mean...
- why?
Because you want to match my level?
Gyeongdo, Lee Gyeongdo!
What should I do then?
Don't you think about my position?
Everyone around me is like me
It's like my house
I can't even think about doing this right now...
Jiwoo, give me some too
It's good to give it time to adapt.
Adaptation?
When people meet people
You need to get used to it or something?
I guess I'm young and don't know much yet.
Or maybe they're poor and don't know
Are you really…
Are you going to keep making things crooked like this?
Why are you doing this more and more?
Jiwooya
Just because I came to my neighborhood
in my neighborhood
At least some good pork cutlet
I want to buy you one of these
Is that really that inconvenient?
I like tteokbokki, not pork cutlet
I originally liked it!
I know!
But I wanted to buy you pork cutlet!
I thought about it from school
To my brothers
I also borrowed money
Just eat some, okay?
Just let me stand upright
Can't we do that?
hi c
I'm sorry
me too
That's because I don't know what's what
Which one?
Why is it so difficult!
the t-shirt you bought me
Why don't you wear that often?
322,000 won that is
my mom one month
This is the money you get if you do a side job.
I am there
You can't do this
I know it really well
My parents work hard
Quite
It was very natural.
But after meeting you
Those natural things
It looks different
I'm sorry
This isn't your fault, but I...
no
I, I'm sorry
Kyungdo, I’m sorry.
I…
That 322,000 won t-shirt
For buying it for me
I'm so so sorry
Jiwoo, that…
I don't think about you too much
I'm really sorry, Gyeongdo.
Let's talk again later
I'll leave for today
I can't connect
Sori Sam after the beep sound
Connected via quick voice
The call fee...
Jiwoo, what's going on?
Why can't I contact you?
I'm so sorry
That's not what I meant.
I was narrow-minded.
Let's see each other for a moment
Should I go closer to home? Jiwooya
Jiwooya
Article Kim!
Yes ma'am
Huh?
Jiwooya
me
갈래
I want to go to New York
uh
Uh, Secretary Yang.
Jiwoo, please help me organize things so I can go to New York.
uh
The sooner the better
Instructions: 611...
Good, good, good!
Hey, wait…
hey! Please get out of the way! hey!
- Let's go to work.
- Gina
It's hardness
How are you?
I'll be fine too
IC
Hey, you're not crazy, you're a real lady
Uh, what is it, Mr.
Hey, hey!
ride
I have to go to work
Hey, the bakery is open at this hour.
Do you want to go to the bakery?
Even if I go now, I’ll be late
It's none of my business
Mr…
-You woke up early.
- I couldn't sleep.
While watching the useful videos you sent me
It leaked so bad
What are you saying?
So what, I
I'm already addicted, is this it?
Is your life ruined or something?
If you drink that much, I can't guarantee it.
Hey, you
I decided to study
Mom said, ‘Aren’t you studying?’ Then
You're pissed, aren't you?
- Take it.
- I need to lose weight, so I plan a diet.
When my boyfriend talks about dieting
You're mad, aren't you?
- I'm angry.
- Yes, you know why you did that?
my algorithm is
He gave me a lot of useful information.
When I see Seo Ji-woo falling asleep at home,
I sent it because I thought it would be good, but was it too much?
No, if you want to cheer me on.
Sit in front and read a book together
Or do some exercise
Isn’t that kind of support?
This kind of guilt
More than a video bomb?
Take it off
What do you say?
Hey, hey, it hurts so much here
Hey, are you okay?
Oh my, there's no blood or tears
Wait a minute, I don't think this is going to work.
Oh, I don't think this will work
Baby, it hurts so much
Hey, are you all gone?
Then I have to go to work.
Wow, she has a very good temperament
As you get older, your temper dies.
you are real
I wish my temper would come out
Instead of the dirt, you stepped on it
I was able to find information without any hesitation.
I'm not good enough
What are you doing?
- You wash your feet.
- Oh, here…
The soil is buried in ancient times.
Where?
- here?
- Boy, really.
Ah, hey, try it.
- Hey
- Oh my!
Baby, try it
It's buried right here, huh?
What, did you roll over when I wasn't looking?
Well, hey, over there, over there
- here, here
- Uh, where?
- here
- Here? It's here too
That's enough
Fish oil, really, I can’t even wash my feet.
What is this doing again?
You shave your feet
really
stand
you do it
Anyway, it takes a lot of work, ah, really.
Don't shake it, just wipe it.
Oh, really
He said he stayed all night
It’s a nuisance if you have an accident while dozing off.
Anyway
Lee Kyung-do is cool.
But what is the ending?
Are you going again?
- Uh
- When?
Do you want to go if you get angry?
Don't even think about companies
Who do you like?
Jiwooya
I told my mom
I know everything
My sister told me
I thought about it.
Why did my father write in his will?
Did you put my stake like that?
'Seo Ji-woo
Jarim Apparel’s inauguration as managing director and’
‘Stake payment after 2 years of maintenance’
I do this myself
It's about defense.
Even if she is not Chairman Seo’s daughter
Is your contribution to the company great?
Don't put anyone in the mouth
It's not eaten raw.
Why do you run away when you know?
It's my dad's company.
You raised me like your own daughter
It's overflowing, sister.
My shares are in the sale of the company
How can this help?
Major shareholder CEO Seo
It won't move
Is it meaningful?
Don’t worry about CEO Seo’s shares.
It will be organized naturally
What's important is the manager's decision.
I can't discuss it with CEO Seo.
This important
problems that can be dangerous
I'm discussing it with the executive director.
I also bet everything.
Now is the time to throw it
If there are more, I have to organize them in a hurry.
I don't even get my money's worth.
I heard enough explanation last time.
What I think is a little strange
Today, CEO Seo works day and night.
I'm stuck on work at work
The clothing business is on the decline no matter what.
Jarim Apparel is not suffering a loss.
But why the company
Should I sell it?
It's time to throw
Why now?
CEO Seo Ji-won, I can’t work for long.
I'm the only one in this company who knows
Well, now Executive Director Choi knows.
What are you saying?
The company owner will soon
It's going to collapse.
That person is very sick
Well, to my family too
I'm hissing
Write, I don’t know.
In less than half a year
Symptoms will become more serious
You mean increased taxes?
Is it terminal, something like that?
Alzheimer's, dementia
What about Seo Ji-woo?
Even though I don't have any shares
He is the son of the previous president.
Oh my, Executive Director Choi
Don’t you know Seo Ji-woo?
Except breathing
I'm a kid who can't do anything productive.
Are you thinking about going abroad and having fun?
What is he doing?
It's not 'him'
Your name is offensive.
If the company is sold
What benefits do I get?
Manjar, please take men's clothes.
Running my own company
It's a dream
It's good
Come on, eat, eat.
Representative Seo, you don’t notice, right?
I drink coffee a lot because I like it so much.
But what kind of medicine is this?
It looks like there's no reaction at all.
I don't know anything about that
Because I'm sensitive
Be more careful not to get caught
Is it a drug that kills people?
Somehow I should know too
I'll be a murderer then
Because it’s not that kind of drug
Do your job well
I really liked what you said
- Yes, please come in.
- Come in, yes.
Longitude, longitude
Kyungdo, let’s go home and sleep, okay?
wake up
lean on mom
- It’s longitude.
- What should I do? It's cold. Huh.
- Let's go home.
- Yeah, I guess I'm drunk.
Should I report it?
Longitude, longitude
Come to your senses, okay?
Let's go home with mom, okay?
It's hardness
I was surprised, this…
Mom, when I'm in the middle of drinking
Instead of falling asleep on the street somewhere
I came here and fell asleep
Still, wasn't that a good thing?
Disgrace, disgrace, oh my
Did you come to meet me? Was it night shift?
Yeah
mom
Please put one person on the list.
name
Uh…
Just call me Kyung-do’s friend.
What should I pray for?
kid, no
Well, there's nothing to do
mom
Are you a kid? ‘Mom, Mom’
Why are you doing that?
- Mom, Mom
- huh?
no my friend
drinking too much
But if you look closely
Living is all about getting drunk
Because it's frustrating
I keep reaching for alcohol.
I know that feeling
I'm sorry for that time
But this one
What should I do?
I don't know if it will help
Go far away
But if you go there
I don't even know anyone
I'm not going to drink any more
I'm really worried
I think I'll be a guest in England
How was your treatment?
- me?
- Well, I don't think there was anything like that.
Whatever happens, I won't drink.
If someone does this
I don’t think I’ll think about alcohol.
There must have been
There was
That's not mom and dad
It's annoying
Of all the mothers I know
I think my mom is the funniest
If you give me a position with something funny
I already got a sermon
Cheer up, Mom.
Cheer up, take care of Jiwoo.
Something I've never done in my life
I have to be a mother
Why do you know everything?
I'm mom
What choice did mom make?
What kind of life are you living?
I'm not interested
It's dad and mom's job.
What makes me angry is
What is Jiwoo’s crime?
Why is my mom like this?
Do you hate Jiwoo?
Why this indifference?
I am completely interested
How do I erase it
Will my mom notice me?
As a recognized child
Can you make it, everything!
I should have just left it alone
I'll live the way I like then
How did this happen?
Until the end, Mom kept Ji-woo…
Please contact me when you are discharged from the hospital.
I'll send secretary Cha.
"Jarim"
"Jalim Apparel"
What is it?
This is a quick message from the managing director.
Well, where did it come from and what is missing?
I checked and
Even the quick driver doesn’t know.
yes
Are you receiving treatment well?
What kind of medicine was it that he quietly obtained?
I'm curious
Why don't you answer the phone?
Doojin Kim?
yes?
delicious? Eating alone
Would you like one?
I come to my senses
You came to your senses
Let's come to work
Yes? yes
Reporter Doojin
The photo search is very special.
It came out so slyly
Where did you get the photo?
I searched patiently
me slightly
I feel like I'm going to chew on it...
I'm not the manager
I'm eating it because it's delicious
It's delicious, right? Ah, you really know the taste.
Yeah
Is this okay?
I think my agency will call me.
This photo fits the suspicion of tax evasion.
Well said, it's a suspicion, suspicion
Deputy Director, I looked into everything.
Accurate fact check...
Hey, wait a minute, what's coming now?
Something red is coming, now
Ah, this distance is a threat.
They say all sorts of things, what, threats?
The conductor had a photo.
Catching juniors is a threat.
Isn’t that right, Kim Doo-jin?
You are right.
Have you ever been hit in the nose with that baseball?
No. Does this nose look like that?
Look at this stretch, this
Does it look like a nose that was reconstructed after collapsing?
I'm really stressed out, really.
Good job junior
Don't stress and go
- Where are you going?
- Director's Office
I'm in big trouble
Huh?
What's wrong with your face? What are you worried about?
I’m in good condition…
Hey, breaking through that competition rate
If you're going to Chicago, the look on your face is
It needs to be a little flashy
Doesn't it work?
Overseas training in the entertainment department
you are the first
- thank you
- Oh, what?
You were chosen because you performed well.
Do I have power?
Anyway, thanks to you
Our Dongwoon Ilbo
It has become the preferred medium for actors.
I'm embarrassed because you praise me so highly.
That's not true, man
think about it
Thanks to your article
Well, all the unpaid actors got paid.
That big evil company closed down!
Recruiting artists these days
If it’s Dongwoon Ilbo, it’s number 1, number 1
I did a good job
Continue with this momentum, okay? Okay?
After studying for a year
Write another one like this
What about Dongwon?
My friend went to see me alive
Ah, Hoengseong Korean beef.
I lost to the snack party.
Are kids really chickens?
Uh, this is gone.
Hey, I haven't chewed this a few times.
It's gone
It really melted, melted, melted
Hey
Hey, I went on a business trip, huh?
I stopped by Hoengseong and bought some beef.
Our Jeongmin has grown up.
I have some hardness too, I have no energy.
If you're going to buy something like this
It would be nice if you text me in advance.
Then I ate my lunch leisurely.
Even if I buy it and give it away, you don't mind, huh?
Today is the weekend
Do you know how much traffic there is?
But I still want to feed you guys
I didn't do my best
So, while I'm doing my best
If you texted me
It couldn't have been better, I guess.
- Don't be rude.
- I will eat well.
Enjoy your meal
Um, oh, right, you have a house.
If you go to Chicago
What are you going to do with that house?
- why?
- No, in a year anyway.
It's okay to unpack
- Give me Yonsei and go.
- Yonsei?
I know someone who works in Singapore.
About a year? They say they are coming to Korea
He's looking for a house too
It would be nice if I could rent your house.
Since she's a girl, she'll write cleanly.
How much should I take?
Hey, who is it?
Go to training for free
Uh, I get rent too.
Isn't this it?
Well, the poor get richer and the rich get richer, huh? You bastard
In everything, the poor get richer and the rich get richer.
When are you leaving?
uh…
I still don't know exactly what
I watched it gradually
Why?
Jiwoo can't show up because she's solo?
Hey, what are you talking about?
What does he have to do with Chicago?
yes you
You need to stop getting involved with Seo Ji-woo.
He lives well on his own
What is living well?
I drink alcohol all the time
Talk about running away
He needs to stop drinking, drink
And if you go out alone
There is no one to stop me
How much more do you want me to drink, huh?
Be honest, you
Because of Seo Ji-woo, you are now
It's Chicago and Nabal.
What, are you not paying attention?
No, baby
Because I can't come to my senses
And if I leave now
And their house too
Kinda kid, there's something like that
You should stop!
Why are you raising your voice like that, huh?
No, this guy
Take a look, huh?
Also, because of Seo Ji-woo, Mr.
How much you love Seo Ji-woo
I don't know what happened
Us too, huh?
We love you so much too
You bastard
kid, what
Can I get drunk just by drinking water?
Yeah, you drink water, water
Let’s leave this good snack and
Drinking water, we
We're afraid you'll die then, huh?
how much we do every day
Do you know if I'm anxious? uh?
But you are now
Worry about Seo Ji-woo drinking too much
Are you doing it, you bastard?
Ai, ah…
Ah, sir…
Then this week
Let's do it like this
yes
Oh my
- Let go
- It's mine.
What, can I buy you coffee?
Hey, it's just water
Just water…
To keep drinking this great drink
Did you take leave?
You can't cause trouble to the company.
Hey, you said it well, huh?
Ministry of Culture ace Lee Gyeong-do
Why did it get to this point, huh?
2 billion counterfeit pictures
After digging for a year
The guy who was into the art world
Why are you doing this?
Hey, thanks to you I
I also got a conductor.
why are you like water
Danny drinks
Why, Gyeongdo!
Hey, Lee Kyung-do
sorry
Senior, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
Let's go, stop drinking.
Bro, I need a drink.
I need a drink
I don't do it
I'll pay the proxy fee
- Huh?
- agency fee, agency fee
I'll give you a proxy fee, have a drink, have a drink and go.
Okay, let's go now
- It’s been a while since we last saw each other.
- Hey, that won't work.
- Let's go and have a drink.
- Hey, a little.
- kinda
- Let's go and have a drink.
Okay, okay, okay
Just one bottle
Just one bottle, okay?
- It’s longitude.
- Okay?
- Hey, this…
- what?
-Why is it like that?
- Fish oil, really.
- Hey, hey, hey
- Longitude!
Wait, wait, wait, wait
I'll do it, I'll do it
- Be careful, be careful.
- Hey, hey, hey
Boy, really
Wow, really!
Uh, I'm fine.
- I'm fine.
- Sit down!
Oh boy, I fell down
I'll calculate it and come back
Hey, I can wake up too!
Get your shit together, man!
Wow, Mr.
I can wake up too
Longitude!
It's hardness
Kyung-do, grab your mom.
Oh, don't do it!
Your mother was hurt
You broke your arm
Why, why, why?
A drunk son
I fell because I was pushed
Wow, Mr.
It's hardness
mom
I'll get treatment well and get out.
don't worry here
mom
yes
Mom, I'm sorry
I'm sorry
brother
Why are you like this? It's gross
I'm so touched today
That's why
I'm full
Can you pack my share?
Seyoung, you have a scale.
Just give me 600 grams
Kiss me
I said I came to run an errand.
Jeongmin’s brother’s errands
Jeongmin hyung
You're in the used car business.
You travel around the country
Today I went to Gangwon-do
On the way, I ate Korean beef in Hoengseong.
I bought it, you know what I mean?
Even mine
I know there's no way I can buy it
Now
Do one point
Are you here to spy?
- Serving as both a business and a business
- You don't even say no.
Are you not eating?
I ate
No, washing dishes
Shouldn’t the person who ate it have to do it?
The child has no conscience
This...
why?
Going
I will come and visit often.
Just give up the thought of drinking, okay?
-Are you a gangster?
- He is a foster guardian.
Who entrusted it to you?
Huh? who?
Me in the past?
what?
It's cool
cool
Me in the past, ha
Dividing movies and dramas
You mean inefficient?
Yes, even entertainment shows
It is divided into two and three parts.
Then, artists
There are cases of overlap.
Articles may be duplicated
That's right, last time I
I set up an interview for Jo Seok-hyun's drama.
Deputy Director Jo Seok-hyeon Entertainment News
You hit first, remember, bro?
what? Latitude, longitude?
Uh, so now
Artist representative
Wouldn't it be better to decide?
Don't divide it into programs.
Yes, while following the program
Big artists
Decide on a person in charge
Yeah, in a more efficient way.
It would be better to divide up the work.
Okay, one person
I guess I'll have to take on more than one, then.
Intern, who likes interns?
All idols are good
Are you kidding?
- Stop it.
- Yes?
Tell me to stop, just keep going
- Stop what, what?
- Okay then.
- IC
- Starting next month
I decided to redo the division of work.
Hey, block it, block it
- Next to me
- Give it to me there.
go forward
Left, left!
It's late
It's hell to come here after work.
Why are you calling me here?
I'm honest
Should I go to England or not?
Even then, barely
It took courage to come forward.
Since you caught me, I pretended to be caught.
Sometimes I think it would be better to stay here
But now I really have to go
If you're doing well, why are you beeping again?
more because of you
It became clear
It's right for me to go to England
I keep imagining it
What you say, grunting kindness
Cheering amidst harsh words, worried eyes
All of these things have meaning.
I keep saying
This is Seo Ji-woo from Joowon University.
I can imagine
I keep coming here
you're not here anymore
Now if you catch me again
At that time, you are also confused.
You just confessed to me that you wanted to date me.
I told you it was pretty
To be exact, I said she was pretty.
I didn't say it was pretty
It was an encouragement not to swear.
Without even thinking about it
If you just say things like that, huh?
Are you an asshole?
Don't do that
My heart says so openly
Get attached, don't do that
Now if you catch me again
At that time, you are also confused.
Hey
Ha, it's been a while
I didn't change my password.
Why are you so surprised?
Well, still in detention center
Did you know it would be there?
uh…
Let's go out, if you have something to say, go out and say it.
I'll be there soon, yeah
I was just passing by
I came here because I thought of you
Jin-eon, I’m a little uncomfortable.
Jiwooya
Let's get back together, okay?
Yeah, baby, I get winded a lot
I smoked it and put your heart through a lot of trouble.
i am sorry
I was wrong, really, really wrong
I also stopped taking medication.
Jiwoo, do you want to see it, okay? Yeah
Now that my probation is over,
I'm going to join my father's company.
Jarim is not interested
I'll just start over from scratch
Let's start together, okay?
I’m not interested either.
Hey, Jiwoo
Jiwoo, yes, Jiwoo
Jiwoo, you
without me
Like this, without my family
Do you think you can live a good life?
Jiwoo, you are now
Well! past twelve o'clock
Raggedy Cinderella, huh?
Who would want to leave you there? Prince?
It's going to be infested with mice.
Huh? Jiwooya
Hey, if you just say what you have to say, I will…
uh?
What is it, Jiwoo?
I bought 2 servings of kimbap.
There is a guest
Jiwoo, where does it hurt?
Like a puppy caught in the rain
Why are you doing this?
You are the person in that photo.
Ah, sir, ah
Time is running out to welcome guests
I think it's a little late
The customer seems to be there.
What's going on? huh?
Dragging a suitcase at this time
What is it, Jiwoo?
You should look here and tell me.
You're talking to me.
What is the situation?
I'm flirting
I'm doing my best
Lee, uh, what is it?
Why is it so deep
Dad, isn’t this overlock?
Hey, not even my mom wears this much.
Aig
Throw it away, what can I do to repair it?
Hey, mommy has changed.
You have to save to live well
Is that what you cherish?
Cheongseung, Cheongseung, throw it away, throw it away
That's my favorite doll!
Attachment doll?
crazy guy
So, get married!
It tastes good
You crazy guy, I'm going to another laundromat! Mr. Lee
Oh my
Did I raise her with less milk?
At that age
What the fuck is wrong with attachment dolls?
Do you want to sleep together?
Is the bed wide?
When I get off work here again today
You should be seen as a loser.
I'm not crazy
Calling that far away
It's not flirting, it's not threatening.
Have you tried it?
Okay, let's go.
- It’s longitude.
- You will make a person and move on.
If you're talking about that, don't say it.
It's nice to see you without speed
how long have i
do i love you